https://www.bio-cat.com/privacy-policy/

Resources
What Are Enzymes?
877.912.4622
At BIO-CAT, we respect your privacy and protect the information you share with us.  This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with information about how we use, store,and protect confidential information.
Your Consent
By using our website and specifically by filling out one of BIO-CAT’s online forms or using one of our chat features, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as is described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this website. This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 10, 2018.
Use of Personal Information
We use the information you give us to provide you information you request. For example, if you fill out a form requesting more information about BIO-CAT, we will use the information you provide us to contact you about BIO-CAT. We may also use information you provide us or information we collect to help us improve your experience on our website.  We will not sell, rent, exchange or share your personal information with any third parties without permission or except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The Type of Information We May Collect
If you fill out a form with BIO-CAT online, we may collect your contact information, such as name, address, email, and telephone number.
When you visit our website, we may also collect your internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, computer or mobile device type, or navigation and clickstream information. This information is used to help us improve users’ experience our website.
Correcting and updating your information
We retain the information you share with us for as long as we need to in order to provide you the services you request. We also retain other data generated by you (i.e., data generated when you browse our website) in a depersonalized or aggregated form in order to help us improve users’ experience on our website. We may also retain your information for a reasonable period of time for BIO-CAT to conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or other legitimate business interests.  If you believe any personal data we maintain about you is incorrect or incomplete, you may ask us to correct it. In addition, you may ask for a copy of it, or you may ask us to delete it. If you have a request about your data or any concerns about the information you provide to us, please contact us at 877-912-4622.
Where your data may be sent
If you are located outside of the United States, we may transfer the personal data you provide to us to the United States. By sharing your data with us, you consent to the transfer of your data to the United States.
Cookies
We use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels, ad tags) to recognize you and/or your devices on, off, and across our different websites. You can control how cookies are used through your browser settings and other tools.
Children’s Privacy.
We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent, unless permitted by law. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.
Your California Privacy Rights.
(a) California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We do not share personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. (b) California residents who are registered users may also request and obtain removal of content. You may request such removal by emailing us at marketing@bio-cat.com. In your request, please provide a description of the material that you want removed and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material, and include your name, email address and the subject line “California Removal Request” so that we can process your request.
Contact Us
Company Name*Contact Name*
First
Last
Phone*FaxEmail*
Enter Email
Confirm Email
Website
Address
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
CountryCountryInterested InAnimal NutritionAgricultureAquacultureBakingBrewing & Alcohol ProductionCane Beet Sugar ProcessingCleaningDairyDietary SupplementsFood, Beverage, & IngredientsFruit & Vegetable ProcessingProbioticsProtein ProcessingSeptic & Drain CareSilver RecoveryWaste TreatmentOtherHow did you hear about us?*AdTradeshowEmail MarketingGoogleReferralPast CustomerSocialNews ArticleAssociationMessage*Consent to Contact*
I consent to this website's Privacy Policy
EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
MENU
Our Company
Our Story
The BIO-CAT Advantage
Our Staff
Quality Policy
Certifications & Organizations
Products
Resources
What Are Enzymes?
News
Patents
Brian Huffman Scholarship
Careers
Contact Us
We use cookies on BIO-CAT.com to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. By clicking accept, you agree to our use of cookies while you are visiting our website.AcceptPrivacy Policy
